(laughs)
(Leonard:)Why is that funny?
(Sheldon:)I don't know.
I like the pain of others.
(laughs)
(Leonard:)Oh, well,
then you'll enjoy this.
(Leonard:)Bernadette does the same thing
with you and Koothrappali.
(Howard:)No, she doesn't.
(Leonard:)She defends him all the time.
(Howard:)She does not.
(Amy:)Who told you
to stop making
(Amy:)all those Gandhi
jokes about him?
(Howard:)Well, she did.
(Howard:)And human resources.
(Leonard:)Who do you think
told Koothrappali
(Leonard:)to go to human resources?
(Leonard:)Son of a bitch.
(laughs)
(Leonard:)You're right, it feels good.
(Penny:)All right,
it's almost game time.
(Raj:)Get it?
Game of Thrones, game time?
(Stuart:)Two women, huh?
(Game of Thrones theme
playing on TV, knocking on door)